it's the market implied probability of a
rate hike has now been priced out for
the years if we take a look at a six
month tenure we're now at 70 basis
points versus just a couple months ago
when we were around 75 is this the right
one um so I think it's right that the
market-based probability has come down I
think that the markets were probably too
hawkish anyhow every economic indicator
in the UK has rolled over except for the
employment data which is by the way the
lagging indicator so I think we probably
just have to wait for that I think
anyone who thinks that we really do need
to see significant rate hikes or more
than one rate hike this year is looking
at the employment data and they're
noting that you know we have real wage
growth in the UK now so there has
actually been wage growth in the UK in a
way there hasn't really been in the US
or most of the rest of the developed
world and that's just maybe you know we
get wage pressures maybe there should
there should be fundamental pressure
upward pressure on inflation and so
maybe the Bank of England should be
hawkish but offsetting that is the
growth outlook and that remains pretty
weak it's funny that yeah and that seems
to be the pointing to his credibility as
how does he walk that loop and ER
sentence had a great tweet earlier he
said another poor decision by the MPC
keeping interest rates at 50 basis
points despite nine years of economic
recovery a buoyant global economy above
target inflation and the lowest
unemployment rate in 43 years a failure
of monetary policy strategy and
leadership yeah I think that's a bit
unfair um a lot of the inflation has
come off the back of the huge
depreciation in sterling after brexit
and that's falling out of the year in
your comparison so we are seeing
inflation actually slow in the UK that
should continue offsetting that is some
wage pressures but you know they're not
runaway wage pressures we finally have
real wage growth as opposed to
contraction in the UK so I don't think
it's something that the Bank of England
needs to be worried about needs to feel
like they have to quick get in front of
and hike rates about so you know the UK
when the Bank of England stuck between
look you know protecting their inflation
mandate and also trying to protect the
growth outlook
they've always erred on the side of
growth this is that you know the rate
hike that we already saw saw them
actually diverge from that and actually
support inflation but I think probably
they will err on the side of